Hi, in this fashion, I'd like to do a quick overview of what prompts are in community of
Avasam compiler to repository. So might be something could be useful for you. I would say
like, the prompts are quite complex. I found here, so there might be some specific situations,
but they will show you several, I like more of us, and you can read just be more over what you
can write in prompt files, might be you can adopt them for your needs, or might be you can
copy paste some parts of these prompts and use by your own. Okay, let's start with the feature
implementation prompt. The goal of this prompt is plan and application, plan a feature, so you see your
like kind of software engineer responsible for creating large tasks project and blah blah blah
and Europe in the Promican find some output formats that I would like to get some MD files with
documentation. We have separate MD file per epic per feature name, and for example, we also describe
what is the folder structure, how where we have app services packages and etc. And compile it
normally will plan all the features for the company project. And we also describe some technical
considerations, so what you need to do. It's quite a big prompt, so you can take a look into this,
but just you know that you can do some planning using copilot. Another prompt is much more
simple. This prompt is from a transformed Python script into polish beginner friendly project,
you can adopt it by JavaScript project. So what it does is it repactor code, it adds some comments
like using some beginner friendly instructional tone, explain it to part of the code,
focus on the logic, so generate some MD files. So we can use that prompt when you have some
project, for example, you download it from a GitHub. It's new for you and you'd like to
a bit simplified and have instructions everywhere, so you can use this prompt just a bit
adopted for JavaScript language. So the next one is interesting, it's for creating a readme files
for the project. You see, we say that the eye has role of senior experts of our engineer,
blah, blah, blah, with extensive experience in source project, and it always makes sure the
generate, generate readme files. We share some like inspiration examples of the readme files
and mentions of what sections include and what modern code, and it then should generate the readme
file for us, but it also can be useful. So the next one is interesting, and we're saying
the goal of this prompt is, as you see, create like setup your instructions and prompts for your
application, we just say that the eye is a GitHub compiled, especially for setup or workflows, and we
say, okay, ask us about the languages we use, about project type, about some additional technologies,
about theme size, about development cycle, how we develop features, and it's heteros,
what bottoms we use, and then you create automatically the custom instructions for us,
create some personal instructions for us, for different languages, but testing for the
documentation for security, for performance, for code review, if you generate some prompts,
the right test, do the code review to the factor code, the setup component,
it also will set up some chat modes, some workflows, so it's really interesting one, and it has
also more rules, how to write the rules, how to, sorry, how to do not write rules and what is a
version of correct, and you can read this one, it also display to compile the file structure,
how everything should be structured, and some examples of the prompts how they should look like,
this one is really powerful, you can try to use it when you just start the project, and you'd
like to have everything set up with all the instructions, if you don't like the instructions,
you can just discover something from them or just delete some parts, you don't like it,
but at least it will give you some ideas and some instructions and ready prompts,
you can use for your project at the setup stage, and the last one in our list is
just JavaScript script, just prompt, for writing test, you see some test structure, some rules,
which it should follow, so we can use it when we would like to write some unit tests,
so we see a lot of rules and some matures for the just, so I'll actually use different functions.
I hope this overview was interesting to you and it give you a clear vision of what is the prompts,
how other use them and what kind of path you can solve with the prompts, okay, see you in the next
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.